從2027年7月29日起
On 29 July 2027 the law will come into force -
取消人類身體豁免權的法律正式生效
which cancels the human body's immunity.
人們開始可以自由的出賣自己的身體
People are free to sell their bodies, how they want.
自此 人類身體開始自由貿易
The human body has traded freely.
巴黎 2035年三月
Paris, March 2035
我剛到法國的時候只有10歲
I was ten years old when I arrived in France.
那時候這片土地還十分繁榮
Then the land was still prosperous.
而今 這裏充斥著1500萬個失業者
Today, there are 15 million unemployed
和無數無家可歸者
and many more are homeless.
國家赤貧
The state is destitute.
巨頭企業掌握著大量的政府債務
Large companies have bought government debt.
他們屬於國家
They are owned by the state.
他們修改了自己的法律
They have changed their laws.
以獲得更高的自由
There are more freedoms.
人們可以自主的買賣自己
People are free to sell themselves,
使用毒品然 後悄無聲息的死去
using drugs and die.
人們還有投票權
People still vote for the government -
但真正的掌權者
but the rulers live
住在遠離亂世的摩天高樓裏
in the skyscrapers.
依然有人相信一切都會改變的
Some cope hope that everything will change yet.
我們不是意大利豬
We are not guinea pigs!
很多人失去了希望 只想茍延殘喘
Most of it is lost hope. They just want to survive.
而我不在意
I do not care.
我有工作 我的工作是取悅他人
I have work. I entertain people.
我是一個競技場的格鬥士
I fight in the arena.
興奮劑合法之後比賽收到了很多人的追捧
Event began when doping was legalized, and is favored.
3月13日
Drago against Ares.
德拉對陣阿瑞斯
Come to this match on 13 March.
公司贊助數百萬
Companies are investing millions of sports -
而獲勝者將為他們的產品打廣告
and the winner will have to advertise their products.
我曾是其中一員 我曾是他們中最優秀的
I was one of them. I belonged among the best.
我用的都是最好的興奮劑
I used the best of doping substances.
而一次我嘗試了一個新產品
Then I tried a new product
就是那次導致了我的中風
and I got a stroke.
已經過去十年了 從那之後我一文不值
It's been ten years. After that I was not worth anything.
譯名: 戰神阿瑞斯
*
-你還記得自己的名字嗎 -去你媽的
Do you still remember your name? -Go to hell.
別倒下 不然就沒人看了
Keep it up, so there is no need anymore to watch you.
瑞達 教練花的是你的錢
Reda, the coach is your money.
感覺還行吧
Interested gig?
當然
Sure.
-這只有500 -凱斯蒂只有兩場
Here are just 500. -Kestit only two rounds.
你
You.
你下一個 你
You're on next. You.
你
You.
還有你
Even you.
裏面來
See you in.
-幹什麼 -什麼都干
What to do? -Myönnyt just everything.
-我現在算是警察了嗎 -就這幾天
Am I now a cop? -This days.
-工資什麼時候付 -把工作做完再說
When will the salary be paid? -When the work is done.
-這是幹什麼-防止你說蠢話
What is that? -It prevents you from asking stupid.
不要人體試驗
NOT experiments
傻逼
Swine!
走
Let go!
多尼維亞是無政府主義者主要攻擊的目標
Donevia is the main target of the anarchists.
公眾情緒太壞 對局勢沒有好處
After a bad quarter, the bad publicity does not do good.
目前 激進分子在總部門口抗議
Currently, activists are protesting in front of the head office -
要求人體試驗立即停止
and require that human trials will be terminated immediately.
新武器法規定全國禁止槍械
The new Weapons Act with firearms are illegal throughout the country.
如果你看見任何違法現象
Please call 08-911-911,
請撥打08-911-911
if you see anything.
新武器法規定全國禁止槍械
The new Weapons Act with firearms are illegal throughout the country.
-你為什麼有槍 -敵人也有
Why do you have guns? -Vihollisemme are armed.
他已經很近了
He was again closed.
我們在多尼維亞那兒看見的
Olimme front Donevian.
謝謝瑞達
Thank you, Reda. -Anouk, thank enoasi.
-法西斯嗎 -是的混蛋
Fascist. -Hemmetin brat.
他太過了
One day, he goes too far.
他什麼時候能控制住自己了
Ai shall he go too far?
-你看 -實驗已經花費了220億歐元
Look. Operating result of EUR 22 billion.
特赦發現
Amnesty estimates that kokeissanne
今年已經死了2千人了
have been killed this year 2000 people.
這什麼時候才能結束 沒人知道
When will this end? -Kyse of accidents.
當局者很清楚這些風險
Participants are aware of the risks,
死者的家屬拿到了賠償金
and the families receive compensation.
沒人逼人民去做什麼
People are not forced to anything.
他們不告訴你這其中的風險
They do not tell you of the risks.
因為這些藥品的效果更好
All of this just because of better performance-enhancing drugs.
瑞達 這是我們的 新老闆
Reda, Boris has a new boss.
以前那個哪去了
Where the former had to?
被抓了 他給自己惹了太多麻煩
Jailed. He had had too much trouble.
-別待在這裏 -總有人要說出真相
Do not stay here. -One of must tell the truth.
-去他媽的真相 -那正義怎麼辦
Shit the truth. What about justice?
我比較看重錢
I like more money.
你怎麼來了
What took you?
-你要鑰匙嗎 -不了 謝謝
Do not want to still the key? -No thank you.
我沒有給過其他人
I'm not offering it to others.
謝謝你照顧我侄女
Thank you for helping my niece.
嗨 安娜
Hi, Anna.
-你好 先生 -怎麼了
Hey. -Well?
-改變分配沒有什麼用 -有多少
Portion size change will not help. -What is your reading?
-超過1 萬 -你不知道準確的數字嗎
More than 10 000. -You do not know the exact readings?
你不會想知道的
Better that you do not know.
我們得有說服力才行
We have to be convincing.
政府想要叫停試驗
The government wants to stop the tests.
他們在等結果
They are waiting for the results.
我已經收到結果了
I received the results.
超過1萬例死亡
More than 10 000 dead?
-叫格鬥士去 -他曾經是很優秀
Tell fighter to. -He was at the top ten years ago.
但現在不行了 他只知道打架
Mediocre, but know how to fight.
作作秀倒是還行
He is perfect for the display.
要讓政府讓步 單贏還不夠
In order for the government capitulates, one win is not enough.
我們得做點什麼
We make it special.
3月13日的競技賽是
13 March arena battles take place European
歐洲錦標賽的資格賽
Championship qualifying matches.
參賽者包括代表波克實驗室的
Included Panzer, arenas serial killer -
連環殺手 裝甲潘澤
which represents the Perk-laboratories.
瑞達坐吧
Reda, sit down.
我有東西給你
I have something for you.
-這是什麼 -這東西能讓你贏
What is it about? -This will help you win.
是你幹的好事 你到底是哪邊的
Is that you're behind this? Whose bread are you?
這是你重振旗鼓的機會啊
This is your chance to get your career in a new rise.
-我可不想死 -誰說你會死了
I do not want to die. -Who talked about the death of anything?
-為什麼選我 -因為你就是個失敗者
Why me? -You are just a loser.
選個弱者比選個強者賺得多
Earn more if I take a loser like if I take someone better.
你自己來 讓我看看
Try it for yourself. I will see what happens.
這藥不適用於所有人
The product does not work for all.
是給你特製的
We have already tested it on you.
我們找蒂爾達要了你的血樣
We asked Tyrolta your blood.
試驗結果非常好
The results were excellent.
我拒絕
I refuse longer tell.
別這樣啊 瑞達 我們可以的
Come on, Reda. We can beat this allocation.
別傻了 這可是你的機會
Do not be stupid! This is your chance.
你就繼續做個弱者吧
then remain a loser.
普羅辛基讓你倍感舒暢自由
Prozyxin help you stay free.
齊托 怎麼樣
How's it going, Zito?
還行
There it is.
-還賣這個 -是啊
Bought for this still? -Ostetaan.
-這個呢 -不賣了明天就停印了
What about this? -No. Printing is stopped tomorrow.
這個呢
What about this?
我準備賣了這個報刊亭 你也知道
I promised to sell the kiosk and you will do it.
別每晚都來煩我了
But do not bother to come here every night.
真是沒完沒了 你該回家好好歇著去
It is one pain in the ass. You would go home to rest.
-1.5萬歐元 是吧 -我們說好了的
EUR 15 000, is not it? -Niinhän we agreed.
-打開 -世界格鬥錦標賽
Eurone. -Tapasimme world champion.
-基因改造的羅德 -換台
Genetically modified Rod... -Euro Zwei.
1千名失業者
"EUR 1 000 unemployed people".
4個失業者對抗一個專業參賽者
Four unemployed against a contestant.
倖存者將獲得1千鎊
One survived to win ￡ 1 000.
大賽獲勝者將獲得10萬歐元 不要錯過
Match winner receives EUR 100 000. This will not want to miss.
-換台 -萊可塔飲料對身體健康有害
Info 34. -Lactia is harmful to health.
動物荷爾蒙和合成維生素
Animal Hormones and synthetic vitamins -
會提高膽固醇含量 破壞細胞
raise cholesterol levels and destroying the cells.
-法西斯 -死基佬
Fascist. -Poof.
你姐姐因為家中持有槍械被捕了
Your sister was arrested from his home in possession of a gun.
-誰 -卡拉·科娃斯基不是你姐姐嗎
Sister of Niko? -Ain't Carla Kowalski is not your sister?
她是兩個孩子的媽媽
She is a mother of two.
他為34信息公司工作
He works Info 34 persons.
和那些無政府主義者 混在一起
He rotates with the anarchists.
他只是需要工作
He needed a job.
那他為什麼家裏有武器
Why he had puoliautomaattiase at home?
有人趁他不注意藏的
Someone has hidden it there without his knowledge.
也有可能他有個恐怖分子朋友
Or maybe he will help a terrorist friends.
-他要坐多久牢 -5到1 0年吧
How much he can get? -five to ten years.
-那槍是我的 -什麼
The gun is mine. -Excuse me?
那個武器是我的
Puoliautomaattiase is mine.
跟我描述一下 樣子 口徑
Tell me the gun, the character and caliber.
你是想幫她
You want to help your sister.
最新消息你們父親跑中國去了
Latest data show that the father moved to China.
你要是不管女孩們 你弟弟會接管
If you do not take girls, Sossu take them.
-我能見我姐姐嗎 -我不能保證
Do I get to meet my sister? -I can not promise anything.
安娜姐姐被認為是恐怖分子
Sister Anne is considered to be a terrorist.
我們要拿這些女孩怎麼辦
What do we do with regard to girls?
-你好 -姐姐昨天被捕了
Hello? -Sister was arrested yesterday.
-你能把她弄出來嗎 -我可以試試
Can you take it out? -I can try to.
找找看他在哪裏
Try to find out where he is.
做完以後我再打給你
Tutkin things and then I'll call.
低調一點
Keep a low profile.
不然 我們就救不出他了
Otherwise we will not get her out.
34信息公司的編輯
Carla Kowalski, Info 34's reporter,
卡拉·科娃斯基近日被捕
has been arrested.
別碰我 我要見我的律師
Do not touch me! My lawyer is here!
卡拉·科娃斯基有兩個孩子
Carla Kowalski has two children.
-瑞達 -讓他一個人
Reda! - Leave him alone.
瑞達 威爾先生是個律師
Reda, Mr Weil is our lawyer.
我們清楚卡拉是被陷害的
We know Carla was staged.
我們有充足的證據
We have waterproof evidence...
別在這兒 過來
Not here. Come on.
你不准參與進來 聽懂了嗎
You do not miss this. Was it distributed?
你這是犯大錯誤
You make a mistake.
懂了嗎
Do you understand?
你這是在犯錯
You make a mistake.
走
Come on.
-你有辦法嗎 -走
Are you finding a solution? - I'm screaming.
等等
You get a minute.
-你怎樣 -還行
How are you doing? -Quite well.
-小孩們呢 -他們和我在一起 挺好的
What about the girls? -They are with me and are doing well.
謝謝
Thank you.
-你知道槍哪兒來的嗎 -有人闖了進來
Do you know where the gun come from? -Kotiimme broken into.
沒偷走什麼東西 但是留下了那把槍
Nothing has been exported, but the gun was left.
我跟警察說過
I mentioned it to the police.
-我知道怎麼把你弄出去 -到時間了
I know how we can get you out. -Time to go.
別惹麻煩 在這裏我沒法保護你
Stay away from problems. I can not protect you here.
時間到了
Time expired.
瑞達
Reda...
救我出去
Help me out here.
他是這麼說的
Is that what he said?
-吃吧 -媽媽不回家嗎
To eat. -Because the mother comes home?
我不知道 梅伊
I do not know Mae.
-小孩不能喝這個 -別跟他講道理
This is not for children. with -Pitbull is useless to talk to.
你在幹什麼
What are you doing?
吃東西 這可不是什麼好人
Syömään. The guy is bad company.
-你以為你是誰 -吃東西
Who do you think You Are? -Syömään.
一直有人被捕
People are constantly reserved.
你真以為你能打敗
Do you really wish to be against him?
逃跑不是什麼好辦法 我們得抗爭
Running is a revolution. We have to fight in the streets.
晚餐涼了
Food cools.
服從暴力 真是個好警察
Obedient and violent. Perfect for a cop.
你去哪裏
Where are you going?
哪兒都不准走
You will not go anywhere!
安諾
Anouk!
-回來媽的 -你罵人
Inside, goddamn it! -You swearing.
罵人是不對的 你要被罰了
You need to put the euro jar.
你能看她一會兒嗎 我馬上就回
Can you watch her? I will be back soon.
沒問題
No problem.
走
Let go!
傻逼
Idiots!
下地獄去吧
Let go, hell!
出去
Get!
是這個人嗎
Is this huorasi? -Häivy here.
死吧
For him back tomorrow. -Go to hell.
你再靠近我就殺了她
If you come closer, I'll kill the girl.
放她走
Let her go.
-看你幹的好事 -我叫救命了的
EXP's nerves. -I asked for help.
你想害死你媽媽嗎
Do you want that your mother die?
是不是
Do not you?
監獄很危險 我得救她出來
The prison is a dangerous place. I have to get him out of there.
我得付他們錢這是規矩
I'm going to pay, because in such a way this works.
-怎麼了 -來吧 我有你姐姐的消息
So? -Come to visit. I have news about your sister.
進來吧 寶貝 桌上有吃的
Come on in, honey. Food is at the table.
賤人
Cunt.
你姐姐是因為匿名舉報被捕的
Your sister was arrested on the basis of an anonymous tip.
如果有什麼大背景的話 我沒法幫你了
If it would be a bigger story, I could not help.
武器是很危險的東西
The weapons are a serious thing.
尤其是在憤怒的人手裏
Angry people do not want to aseistautuvan.
錢的問題不太好解決
Bad news in terms of money.
-我錢不夠 -多少錢
Little amount is not enough. -Paljonko?
10萬
One hundred thousand.
-這麼多錢能幹什麼 -讓那槍消失
What does it amount to get? -Ase disappears.
你姐姐就能自由了
Your sister will have to be liberalized.
我們得迅速 在案件審理之前
We must act quickly, before the case goes to the prosecutor.
我拿到錢就告訴你
I'll call you when I get the money.
我們要是用這個的話很可能會死
This shows that we may die material.
你不會
You do, however, is the culture.
-你的血對它沒有排斥 -這真的
Your blood does not reject material. -Tuuria indeed...
-還有什麼我需要知道的 -實質效應
Do I need to know more? -Aineen effects.
延遲癥狀比較明顯
Withdrawal symptoms are intense.
比賽之後你可能會昏迷一段時間
You will lose consciousness after the match.
你的心臟有可能受不了這些癥狀
Your heart will take either withdrawal symptoms or not.
但這個我們現在也不能肯定
We can not know it in advance.
所以如果我打贏對手了 也可能被藥弄死
So if my opponent does not kill me, kill agent.
我們只能說這是有風險的
We will tell only that this is risky.
什麼計劃
What is the plan?
我介紹你去歐洲錦標賽資格賽
I must inform you in the European Championship qualifying match.
你得打敗三個對手
You have to be overcome in three installments.
我給你下注 你輸了 我也慘了
Have given the bet for you. You suck, so I told sucks.
但是我們最多能贏回6倍的錢
We can win up to six times the money back.
我有什麼好處
What is my contribution?
如果你能撐過3輪 你就能拿到12萬
120 000, if you can bear three rounds.
然後還有10萬
In addition, you will get 100 000 immediately to hand.
進來吧 你侄女很高興
Come on in. My niece are delightful.
不像你
Unlike you. -Hymyä. You will be described.
相機在那邊
Cameras that side.
視頻會在基佬網上播放
The image is displayed on page gaylife.com.
-是你幹的嗎 -不是
Is this what you do? -I do not.
我是個藝術家 但我也上上網
I drag artist. I can also be viewed online.
-你喜歡人嗎 -我上的時候還是喜歡的
Are you interested in it people? -At least, when I take.
總有人愛看這些東西
Some want to see the shit.
該睡覺了 孩子們 說再見吧
Time to go to bed, girls. Say your friend hello.
-晚安 米索提斯 -晚安 米索提斯
Night, Myosotis. Good night, Myosotis.
晚安 我一直歡迎你們
Goodnight. You are always welcome.
真是
Oh yeah...
不用謝
No problem!
歡迎收看歐洲頻道
Welcome to Eurone channel.
現在來介紹
We introduce European
歐洲錦標賽資格的參賽選手
Championship qualifying tournament contestants.
混混對戰赫拉克勒斯
Cognard against Hercule.
宇宙先生對戰無名戰士
Mr Univers against Soldat Inconnu.
酷小子對戰佛陀 阿瑞斯對戰裝甲潘澤
Cool Dude against Budha. Ares against Panzer.
臥槽 真的假的
Hell! Is not real!
你贏他的比率只有百分之一
Your chances of getting against him was one in a hundred.
你就是個徹頭徹尾的失敗者
You are a loser and yet full of luck.
他贏不了 你還看不清嗎
He can not win, friends are invincible. Look!
波克實驗室的潘澤 不可戰勝的戰士
Panzer, indomitable warrior. Perk-star laboratories.
50勝 13殺
50 PROFIT kills 13
-競技場的連環殺手 -他可不知道輕重
Arenas serial killer. -He knows no punches.
完全是個冷血怪物
Not feeling Areskaan. -He will take just about anything.
他的攻擊得有11.25磅重
His stroke is responsible for 11.25 bar.
就跟汽車撞過來一樣
As would run over by a car.
潘澤只知道怎樣殺戮
Panzer to know how to overcome and killed.
你信不信他5分鐘就能贏
Do you believe that he can win in five minutes?
我相信
I think.
我希望你會贏
I bet behalf of your winnings.
"I bet behalf of your winnings.
去你媽的 我會輸的什麼都不剩的
" Bullshit! I'll lose everything.
他代表93號俱樂部
He represents the Arena Club 93
第一盤就有手下敗將了
and has a first-round underdog.
這是什麼 紀念品
What's in it? Sovereigns for the kiosks.
-多少錢 -將近1.5萬歐
How much? -This with nearly EUR 15 000.
-離10萬歐還差得遠呢 -沒關係
It is far from 100 000 euro. -Not necessarily.
-賭我贏 -你讓我賭嗎
You hit bet on won. -Saako own matches to bet on?
不 我請我朋友幫忙
No, but a friend can ask to do it.
你有朋友嗎
Do you have friends?
-你要我給你賭1.5萬 -是的
Would you like that I bet EUR 15 000 from the front? -I want.
不太可能 你會死在那兒的
Please do not do you no good. You will die there.
我沒問你意見
I did not ask your opinion.
你就能不能下注吧
Can you take these goddamn money?
好吧 我會的
Alright. Omatpa have your money.
你能幫他說句謝謝嗎
he Kuolisiko, if you would thank?
當然
Would die.
今天是週六 歡迎來到
It's Saturday and the euro Ella sport like narcotics.
歐洲錦標賽資格賽
Welcome to the European Championship qualifying matches in pairs.
今晚我們將狂歡到午夜 呈現給您
It will transmit at six to midnight. Also included is 208 contestant -
208個參賽選手的104場比賽
who will box tonight 104 match.
給 喬治
Here. Contact Georges.
比賽結束之後你就能出來了 別擔心
You can come out when the match is over. Do not worry.
波克實驗室今晚最具看點
Star Perk Labs is the favorite in the evening.
他將對戰排名652的阿瑞斯
He faces Ares, whose rank is 652.
阿瑞斯是十年前的巔峰之人
Ares was the best ten years ago.
因此 賠率為12比1
Therefore, the odds are 12 to 1.
似乎潘澤今晚會贏得很輕鬆
It appears that the permit is all too easy to match Panzer -
讓阿瑞斯嘗點苦頭啊
which must point vyölleen a new victim.
請記住
Remember that
你還可以通過歐洲有線收看這場賽事
you can also watch the games via Europlayn.
物質很快就被吸收
The substance will soon begin to be affected.
你有5分鐘
You have five minutes of your time.
看起來我沒辦法了
And it is likely that I did not get away with it.
波克實瞼室的產品出場
Perk laboratory-based product is taken out.
阿瑞斯為白方 潘澤為黑方
Ares fights in white, black favorite Panzer.
僅僅從眼神就可以看出來
Panzeri, judging by the look in their eyes
潘澤會進攻的很兇
Ares must be on guard.
漂亮的直擊
A brilliant uppercut!
-根本沒有進攻 -阿瑞斯已經很不錯了
I have never seen anything beats. -Ares doing well.
挑戰者進攻了 阿瑞斯真讓我們驚訝
The challenger attacks. Ares has surprised positively.
真棒
What a blow!
我們的大師陷入了麻煩
The master is in trouble.
阿瑞斯打的很好
Ares fights impressively.
他又打了一針腎上腺素 這意味著阿瑞斯
He gets another adrenaline surge, which means that Ares...
-還有多久 -不久了
How much time is left? -Vajaa minute.
防禦 阿瑞斯
Protect, Ares!
潘澤輸了
Panzer is the countries.
法國第一名的選手
French number one lost
輸給了一個三流的參賽者
in the second installment of the third-class contestant.
很快
Soon,
我們又要看見一顆冉冉升起的新星了
the market provides a new product.
即使阿瑞斯的支持者也十分吃驚
Even some in favor of Ares bet smitten mahtoivat surprised.
你沒必要幫他下注的
You do not have bet on his behalf.
我根本不知道他能贏
I did not know that he would win.
我跟你說過的
I told you this would happen.
媽的 你贏了
Damn, you're you won!
你贏了
You won!
這個藥品還沒成功 但你已經看到成果了
Product is not ready yet, but you saw what HSX is able to.
該投票了
It's time to vote.
誰想繼續實驗
Who wants to continue the experiments?
排名652的阿瑞斯
Ares, ranked 652,
打敗了第一名的潘澤瑞
defeated number one in the list have been Panzeri.
波克的股票跌了20
Perkin shares fall 20...
-我能來嗎 -可以 已經完了
Can I come? -You can, it already ran out.
-瑞達還好嗎 -我不知道
Is Reda okay? -I do not know.
你可以預見到
You will see for sure the economic
它在軍事和體育上的應用
benefits in the field of military and sport.
我們可以建造
But we can earn billions upon billions of...
成千上萬的工業部門
... in the industrial sector.
想想這能多大的提高生產力吧
Think about how HSX increase employee productivity.
阿瑞斯還活著
Ares is alive. We have found indeksihenkilömme.
-他怎麼樣了 -你叫什麼
How is he? -What is your name?
-下地獄去吧 -他還好
Go to hell. -He's doing well.
-你聽新聞了嗎 -你死了 但你沒事
Did you hear the news? You are dead. You're fine.
被打的很慘啊
Ottelit like an animal.
你有機會贏得冠軍
You could even win the European Championship title.
不了 謝謝 這樣就夠了
No thanks. This was enough.
我要是你 我起碼會聽聽
If I were you, listen at least.
瑞達 多尼維亞的副總想跟你做個生意
Reda, Donevian Deputy Director-General wishes to make an offer.
科娃斯基先生 我希望你是冠軍
Mr. Kowalski, I wish you a champion.
你的身體和藥品的反映很好
Your body will respond well to a substance.
我們希望提供更多幫助
We want to launch the help.
我們和教練商討了費用問題
We discussed the fees with the coach.
-那是什麼 -未來
What is that? Previews.
瑞達過來
Reda came!
-你要這個嗎 -不了
Would not come nigh thee? -No.
-這個呢這個呢 -不
How about this, or this? -No.
噓
It happened. -Wimp.
嘿
Hey.
18萬歐 你可以洗手不幹了
EUR 180 000. You can retire.
去你自己房間
Go to your room.
我得繼續
I'm going to continue.
為什麼 你只是為了媽媽才幹的
Why? You did this because of their mother.
我們把你媽媽救出來以後 還有8萬歐
When we get your mother out, leaving EUR 80 000.
不多也不少 我掙了50萬
We are not rich and not poor. I earn 500 000.
我要是贏了能賺5百萬
I can get five million following the victory.
這是黑心錢 他們犧牲了多少人啊
They are blood money. They kill people in their laboratories.
你知道這是什麼嗎
Do you know what is the reward guinea pigs?
1.5萬條人命
15 000 is the price of a human life.
規則就是這樣 我沒法改變
Rules of the game are what they are. I can not change them.
有錢就可以了
Rich does not capture.
我們可以好好的活很長一段時間了
We can live well and for a long time.
你媽媽下周出來 想想你要怎麼做吧
Your mother gets out next week. Decide what you want to do.
HSX讓人們無所不知
HSX makes people invincible.
HSX比人類更有創造力
HSX creates more than people.
HSX就是人類的未來
HSX is the future of mankind.
你就是那個排名652
You were the French ranking list ranks 652 -
卻打敗了第一名的那個
but did you hit list number one.
感謝你
Thank you for Ares profit,
我的股份漲了53%
the share price has risen more than 53 per cent.
公司的利益會達到320億
The Group's profit will reach EUR 32 billion.
-誰住在這裏 -我們搬過來了
Who lives here? -We we change here.
-米索提斯在哪裏 -在家
Where is Myosotis? -Kotonaan.
這裏好蠢哦
Here is stupid.
10萬
One hundred thousand.
核事故以後這裏被清空了
Drôme department have been evacuated because of the nuclear accident.
法國的失業率超過了一千五百萬
In France the unemployment rate is already more than 15 million.
中國承諾增加對歐洲的補貼
China promises to increase subsidies they pay for Europe.
美國總統承諾
US president promises to overcome
將在2年內結束經濟危機
the economic crisis within two years.
-怎麼了 -被新獄友打的
What happened? -He defended the new prisoners.
-給 -拿著
Here. -Keep them.
找到是誰做的
Find the one who grassed him.
找出是誰藏的槍 為什麼
Find out who hid the gun and why.
我不能保證
I can not promise anything.
如果你缺錢就告訴我
Call me if you need more money.
下一個 挑戰阿瑞斯的鬥士
Next, the presentation fighter to the next point Ares.
桑尼諾夫隊的 拉馬斯
Saninov presents: La Masse.
150磅的重量
150 pounds rage.
無與倫比的身形
Incredible physics -
他就是天生的殺手
like a sumo wrestler. La Masse did not dodge attacks.
嘿
Hey.
-現在你給他們幹活了 -關閉
So now you work for them? -Bracket.
-你能不能換件衣服 -你想幹嘛
You could change your clothes. -What do you want?
你可以幫我們調查
You can help us find
多尼維亞真正的受害者到底有多少
out what is the real number of victims Donevian.
-多尼維亞不是我敵人-她可是你的姐姐
Donevia is not my enemy. -He was your sister.
我在調查為什麼姐姐被送去監獄
I'm looking for hands on them, why my sister was sent to prison.
這可能有用
Maybe this will help.
國家數據
Sister of a national database.
叫做電話箱的信息網
Informant called telephone boxes.
這是地址
Here's the address.
瑞達
Reda!
你在這裏幹嘛 還沒忘掉我這個老朋友啊
What are you doing here? Nice not to forget old friends.
你準備好明天的比賽了嗎 揍死他
Are you ready for tomorrow's game? Crush the guy.
我會賭你贏的
I'm going to bet for you.
還有誰在用這個藥
Who else using the product?
-為什麼這麼問 -我有沒有競爭對手
How so? -Do I have competitors?
你很幸運 你是唯一的
You are the only one. There you have quite lucky.
謝謝你幫我姐姐
Thank you on behalf of my sister.
謝謝你的花
Thank you for the flowers.
不用謝
No problem.
我還需要你幫助
I need your help again.
怎麼了
What is it about?
如果我明天沒有贏
Do you care of the girls,
你能幫忙照顧孩子們嗎
if I go badly tomorrow?
照顧小孩我不在行
Children's education is not my thing.
他們可以住在我鄰居家
They can live in my neighbor's house.
我只是讓你照看一下
I ask only that you keep an eye on them.
好吧
Alright.
謝謝
Thank you.
我們會播出比賽直到午夜
We show the matches until midnight.
今天我們將進行52場比賽的第二輪
Today we conducted a second round of 52 matches.
今天的開場是 阿瑞斯對戰拉馬斯
We will begin today's match: Ares against La Masse.
多尼維亞證明了他的高效
Donevian preparation proved its efficiency -
阿瑞斯上一場比賽最後出了問題
Aresilla but had problems at the end of the match.
今天我們一定要避免
Today we must avoid them.
拉馬斯在法國排名第七
La Masse is the seventh ranking in French.
他正是事業的黃金期
He has just started his career.
16戰16勝
16 games, 16 wins.
上一場比賽他只用了43秒
Last match lasted 43 seconds -
就將他的對手狠狠地壓在了牆上
when he overwhelmed his opponent against the wall of the cage.
賭徒們沒有什麼偏好 比率是1比2
Bettors do not have a favorite. The coefficient is 1, 2.
你確定嗎 吉恩
Are you sure about that, Jean?
規則不變 時間是5分鐘 速戰速決
The same rules. The time is five minutes. Faster onset of action.
我每場比賽都會搜集血樣 開始吧
I'll take a blood sample before and after a match. Let's start.
現在可以大賺一筆了
Now we earn properly.
教練在哪裏
Where is the coach?
只花了17秒
It took only 17 seconds!
這說明HSX沒用
This indicates that the HSX is a dummy.
並不能給你超人的力量
It does not give superhuman powers.
你賭了多少錢
How much did you hit the bet?
醒醒
Top that!
起來
Up.
教練沒有回答
The coach does not answer.
都結束了 大家會要求一個解釋
This is our end. Markets are waiting for an explanation.
查查阿瑞斯 你有4個小時
Search Ares. You have four hours of time.
我需要他幫助
I need his help.
找到他侄女
Find her my niece.
-小孩們準備好了嗎 -是的
Are the girls ready? -are.
-錢呢 -賭了30萬
What about the money? -Laitoin 300 000 bet for him.
60萬歐啊 不開心嗎
EUR 600 000! Not happy?
你怎麼說
Have I not. -How do you say?
拿上錢 一會兒見
Get the money. I'll see you kämpilläsi.
你要是沒看見我 就別等我了
If you do not see me, do not wait.
和孩子們一起走
Get out with the girls and money.
-你可以打這個電話 -她是誰
You can call this number. -Who is she?
朋友 他是警官 可以幫你
Friend. He is a police officer and help you.
-安諾給了他電話 -別管他
Anouk gave Boris number. -Forget him.
有什麼問題的話 警察幫不了你
If something goes wrong, only the police can not help you.
-你會走嗎 -你怎麼看
Will you go? -How do you say?
走 我掩護你
Go or you'll get your back. -Hemmetin macho player.
瑞達回來以後嗎
Since Reda come from?
等等 米索提斯在準備吃的
Later. Myosotis put the food.
等等
Wait!
他不在這裏 他在這裏幹什麼
He is not here. What would he do here?
-他在 -你在幹什麼
He is here. -What are you doing?
我毀了他們 很顯然
I destroyed them. Obviously you do.
-我為你準備了這個 -不
I saved this for you. -No hell.
別讓他注射
Do not let him inject it.
你看見我怎麼對潘澤了的
You saw what I did Panzer.
只有你能用這個
You were the only one who was able to use the product.
你可能能跟我一樣
You would have done the same in my situation.
聽著
Listen.
你姐姐的事我很抱歉
I feel sorry for your sister.
我完全無法想像
I could not have imagined that this would happen.
我只是想要錢
I just wanted that ottelet.
我不想失去這個機會
I did not want to lose this opportunity.
輸掉才比較明智
It was smart to lose.
你支持了你對手
You backed behalf of the opponent,
你把孩子藏起來了
and you hide the girls transu creates.
真遺憾你用了藥
Too bad that you were using a syringe.
你現在沒有了
You would not have it now.
-我侄女在哪裏 -維拉斯打電話
Where are my niece? Villas. Give them a call.
是我的
It's for me.
嘿 瑞達 我和你侄女在一起
Hey, Reda. I am with my niece.
你按他們說的做
You're doing it, what it is told.
他把我介紹給了教練
He introduced me to the coach.
你姐姐的事也是他的主意
Your sister was his idea.
不然你也不會同意用藥的
Otherwise, you would not have agreed to take the medicine.
他真的喜歡你
He certainly likes you.
但更喜歡錢
But money prevailed.
別浪費時間了 你侄女們想見你
Do not waste any more time. My niece will want to meet you.
嘿 米索提斯 信息
Hey. Myosotis. Message.
安諾 米索提斯在這裏 說話
Anouk, Myosotis here. Answer.
他拿到錢了嗎
Hänelläkö have the money?
-多少 -60萬歐
How much? EUR -600 000.
讓他過來
Tell him to come here.
別想耍滑
Do not try anything.
我知道你在那兒
I know that you are there.
你在幹什麼 安諾
What are you doing? Anouk?
你想吃什麼
Hello. -Last. What do you want to eat?
瑞達回家了 他答應帶我們出去吃
Reda already came home and promised to take us to eat.
-真的嗎 -還有你
Really? -You too.
她想謝謝你
She wants to thank you.
真好我就來
That's nice. I'm coming.
爽快的女孩
A brisk girl.
不好意思 我能借一下你的手機嗎
Excuse me, can I borrow your phone?
你想用來(??)
Do you want to kullianikin?
-你要什麼 -要你
What do you want? -Thee.
-為什麼只選我 -30126人的實驗
, Seeing I lost. -Testasimme preparation of 30126 people.
死了30125個人
Of these, 30 125 died.
只有你的身體能承受
You are the only one that your body can tolerate HSX added.
只有你的幫助
With your help,
我們才能開始賣
we can get the formula stabilize and we can start selling.
你真以為我們會放你走嗎
Did you really think that would give you scat?
你好
Hello?
媽的
Damn...
你好
Hello?
我需要槍
I need a gun.
-我侄女在哪裏 -他們馬上就來了
Where are my niece? -They will come soon.
首先你得解釋解釋
First, it is time to explanation.
很高興見到你 科娃斯基先生
Autamme be happy to Mr. Kowalski.
你在比賽之前準備過嗎
Did you preparation before the match?
謝謝 最後一個問題
In the explanation. -Thank you. A last question.
準備期需要多長時間穩定
How long does it take stabilization of the preparation?
兩個月
Two months. -It heard.
兩個月之後 就可以創造超人類
After two months, produced makes whom any over-the human.
理論上可以 67 來這裏
This can affect the abstract. 67, come here.
67 是第一個由轉基因改良
67 is a genetically modified by Svarog.
他是羅德的克隆體 羅德是全世界第一個
He is a clone of Rodin. Rod was number one in the world.
他花了我們2千萬
He cost us 20 million euros.
潘澤的打擊力量有11.25磅
Panzer hit 11.25 bar force.
你自己也見過
You get to witness this with your own eyes.
看看這是誰
See who is there.
是米索提斯
It is Myosotis.
嘿 寶貝
Hey honey.
-你好嗎 -她是誰
Are you okay? -Who is she?
一個朋友 他從沒有什麼好朋友
Enonne friend. He then did not know how to choose friends.
-他是誰 -多尼維亞的頭頭
Where is he? -Donevian headquarters.
現在該自食惡果了開始吧
The product begins to bear fruit. The show can begin.
嘿 瑞達
Hey, Reda!
孩子們都好
The girls are fine.
安諾和米索提斯在等你
Anouk and Myosotis waiting for you.
很愉快的見面
A nice meeting.
你已經看到了 沒必要在留戀
As you can see, mourn without reason.
放下武器 我要活捉他
Put down your weapons. I need him alive.
我說了 活捉
Alive, I said!
三分鐘 別逃了
Three minutes, and is prepared to stop running.
兩分鐘
Two minutes.
是我 你想讓我做什麼
It's me. What did you want me to do?
-有用嗎 -很好 他們走了
Does it work? -Perfectly. They are gone.
你那兒怎樣
How is it going there?
我們在等你 你在幹什麼
We are waiting for you. What are you doing?
你還記得你說過他們的錢嗎
Do you remember what you said of their money?
你說他們都是黑心錢
You said that they are blood money.
我有不好的消息
I have some bad news.
我也是他們的資產之一
I am worth billions of them.
他們不放我走
They did not let me go.
我要是活著他們就不會放過你
They do not leave you alone, if I am alive.
替我謝謝米索提斯
Bless the MYOSOTIS for me.
這是個好結局
This may end well yet.
該結束了
So it ends.
我們對他們來說一文不值
We were just guinea pigs for them.
從2027年十月到2035年三月
From October 2027 to March 2035
多尼維亞殺害了30126人
Donevia killed 30 126 people.
他們在法律的包庇下犯下重罪
They did it within the limits of the law.
自由和平等不復存在
Freedom, fraternity and equality were gone.
星星之火
Revolution is
可以燎原
It took only a spark.
我想他不會隨時間被遺忘
I did not think he would get the time.